Beveridge Collection of Unemployment, Volumes 1-20 on Microfilm 6130 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- London: Central (Unemployed Body of London, Minutes, 1907-1908 (V.13. ). Unemployed, Labour Exchanges, etc., 1887-1914..(V.14. ) (Reel 9)
  - V.14-14 Die Aufarbeitung den monatlichen Arbeitsmarktstatistik des Reichs-Arbeitsblatts, 1914; 15 (Reel 9)
    Germany. Reichs-Arbeitsblatt, Mai 1914. Sonder-Abdruck. Die Aufarbeitung den monatlichen Arbeitsmarktstatistik des Reichs-Arbeitsblatts.
  - V.14-15 Return as to employment of builders and building contractors' workmen, 1905; 16 (Reel 9)
    Charity Organisation Society. Committee on Unskilled Labour, 1905. Return as to employment of builders and building contractors' workmen.
  - V.14-16 Egham Free Registry for the Unemployed, 1893-1894; 17 (Reel 9)
    Egham Free Registry for the Unemployed. a. Eighth annual report, 1892. b. Ninth annual report, 1893. c. Tenth annual report, 1894.
  - V.14-17 Labour Exchange Reports, 1906-1911; 18 (Reel 9)
    Labour Exchange Reports, etc. a. West Ham, County Borough of. Distress Committee. Employment exchanges, 1907. b. Haslemere. Labour Exchange and Unemployment Society. Report and statement of accounts. 1911. c. Edinburgh, City of. Distress Committee. Recommendations re establishment of Municipal Labour Exchange ... 1906. d. Edinburgh, City of. Excerpt from letter from Local Government Board. 1906. e. Edinburgh, City of. Labour Bureau. Superintendent's report for year ending December, 1905. f. Glasgow, City of. For the information and consideration of the Sub-Committee on Labour Exchange ... 1908. Report by the Superintendent for the month of January, 1909. g. Westminster, City of. Labour Bureau. Report of the Superintendent for the 15 months ended 31st March, 1906.
  - V.14-18 Metropolitan Employment Exchanges, 1906; 19 (Reel 9)
    Metropolitan Employment Exchanges. a. London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Report of Employment Exchanges Committee. b. London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Metropolitan Employment Exchanges. Provisional bye-laws. 1906. c. London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Metropolitan Employment Exchanges. Preliminary instructions to superintendents of local exchanges. 1906. d. London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment exchanges and the schools.
  - V.14-19 Labour exchanges, 1906; 20 (Reel 9)
    Joint Board representing the Parliamentary Committee of the Trades Union Congress, the General Federation of Trade Unions, and the Labour Party. Labour exchanges. 1906.
  - V.14-20 Memorandum as to future of Labour Exchanges, 1907; 21 (Reel 9)
    Beveridge (Sir William Henry): Memorandum as to future of Labour Exchanges. 1907.
  - V.14-21 Form of return for Labour Bureaux, 22 (Reel 9)
    United Kingdom. Board of Trade. Commissioner for Labour. Form of return for Labour Bureaux.
  - V.14-22 Copy of the report made to the Local Government Board, 1906; 23 (Reel 9)
    United Kingdom. Labour Bureaux. Copy of the report made to the ... Local Government Board by Arthur Lowry. 1906. 86.
  - V.14-23 Memorandum on Labour Exchanges, 1908; 24 (Reel 9)
    Beveridge (Sir William Henry). Memorandum on Labour Exchanges. 1908. (Confidential)
  - V.14-24 Labour Exchanges Bill, 1909; 25 (Reel 9)
    United Kingdom. Labour Exchanges Bill. Financial Statement. 1909 (Cd. 4710)
  - V.14-25 Labour Exchanges, 1909; 26 (Reel 9)
    Beveridge (Sir William Henry). Labour Exchanges. General Memoradum (Confidential). 1909.
- Unemployment, 1893-1895. (V.15. ) (Reel 10)
  - V.15-1 Unemployed Scotland, 1893-1894; 1 (Reel 10)
    United Kingdom. Unemployed Scotland. Report by the Board of Supervision to Her Majesty's Secretary for Scotland on the relief of the able-bodied unemployed during the winter of 1893-94. (C. -7140).
  - V.15-2 Select Committee on Distress from Want of Employment, 1892; 2 (Reel 10)
    United Kingdom. Select Committee on Distress from Want of Employment: third report ... 1892. 365.
- Unemployed, Metropolitan Employment Exchanges, 1906-1910 (V.16. ). United Kingdom, Labour Dept, Board of Trade, 1908. V.18. Central (Unemployed) Body for London, Reports, 1907-1914. (V.17. ) (Reel 11)
  - V.16-1 Note on employment exchanges, 1 (Reel 11)
    Note on employment exchanges: what they can do.
  - V.16-2 Employment exchanges, 1906; 2 (Reel 11)
    Beveridge (Sir William Henry): Employment exchanges: draft memorandum 1906.
  - V.16-3 Interim report and recommendations on employment exchanges, 3 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Classification Committee. Interim report and recommendations on employment exchanges.
  - V.16-4 Report on the question of employment exchanges, 4 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Classification Committee. Report on the question of employment exchanges.
  - V.16-5 Report of Employment Exchanges Committee, 5 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Report of Employment Exchanges Committee.
  - V.16-6 Strassburg Labour Exchange, 6 (Reel 11)
    [Strassburg Labour Exchange.]
  - V.16-7 Metropolitan labour exchanges, 7 (Reel 11)
    List of Metropolitan labour exchanges.
  - V.16-8 Employment exchanges: salaries per place filled, 8 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment exchanges: salaries per place filled.
  - V.16-9 List of Metropolitan employment exchanges, 9 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. List of Metropolitan employment exchanges.
  - V.16-10 Memorandum on relation of employment exchanges to trade unions, 1906; 10 (Reel 11)
    Beveridge (Sir William Henry). Memorandum on relation of employment exchanges to trade unions. (Confidential). 1906.
  - V.16-11 entral (Unemployed) Body for London, 11 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. (Two letters).
  - V.16-12 Possible future relations with Trade Union unemployed registries, 12 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Possible future relations with Trade Union unemployed registries.
  - V.16-13 Suggestion concerning a system of working between Trade Union branches and employment exchanges, 1907; 13 (Reel 11)
    Lewisham Employment Exchange. [Suggestion concerning a system of working between Trade Union branches and employment exchanges.] 1907.
  - V.16-15 Proposed working arrangement with the Wheelwrights' Operative Union, 14 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Proposed working arrangement with the Wheelwrights' Operative Union.
  - V.16-16 Alteration of rules, 15 (Reel 11)
    [Wheelwrights' Operative Union]. Alteration of rules, etc.
  - V.16-17 Association of Employment Exchange Superintendents, 1907; 16 (Reel 11)
    Association of Employment Exchange Superintendents. (Letter). 1907.
  - V.16-18 Employment exchanges and the schools, 17 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment exchanges and the schools.
  - V.16-19 Central Body meeting, 1908; 18 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Central Body meeting, 3rd July, 1908. Supplementary agenda.
  - V.16-20 Minutes of meeting, 1908; 19 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Minutes of meeting ... 17th July 1908.
  - V.16-21 Minutes of meeting, 1910; 20 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Minutes of meeting ... 21st January 1910. (Vol. V, No. 7).
  - V.16-22 working statistics, 1907; 21 (Reel 11)
    Metropolitan Employment exchanges: working statistics from 20th August 1906 to 31st May 1907.
  - V.16-23 working statistics, 1907; 22 (Reel 11)
    Metropolitan Employment exchanges: working statistics from 1st January to 31st May 1907.
  - V.16-24 working statistics, 1907; 23 (Reel 11)
    Metropolitan employment exchanges: statistics of working for four weeks ending 25th January 1907.
  - V.16-25 Statement showing work done, 1908; 24 (Reel 11)
    Islington Employment Exchange. Statement showing work done ... during the month of March 1908.
  - V.16-26 Report of working, 1907; 25 (Reel 11)
    Hackney and Stoke Newington Employment Exchange. Report of working ... from 1st January to 27th December 1907.
  - V.16-27 Superintendent's report, 1908; 26 (Reel 11)
    St. Marylebone Employment Exchange. Superintendent's report for six months ending June 26th, 1908.
  - V.16-28 Precis of applications for superintendentship, 27 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Precis of applications for superintendentship of St. Pancras.
  - V.16-29 Precis of applications for superintendentship, 28 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Precis of applications submitted for appointment as Superintendents of following exchanges:- Shoreditch, Fulham, Camberwell, Lambeth and Stepney.
  - V.16-30 Precis of applications for superintendentship, 29 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Precis of applications submitted for appointment as superintendents of following exchanges:- Battersea, Bermondsey, Paddington and St. Marylebone.
  - V.16-31 Precis of applications for superintendentship, 30 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Precis of applications submitted for appointment as superintendents of following exchanges:- Bethnal Green, Deptford, Greenwich, Southwark, Wandsworth and Woolwich.
  - V.16-32 Linking up with extra-Metropolitan labour bureaux, 31 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Linking up with extra- Metropolitan labour bureaux.
  - V.16-33 Office hours, 32 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Metropolitan Employment Exchanges. Office hours.
  - V.16-34 Superintendent's report, 1908; 33 (Reel 11)
    [Bethnal Green]. Superintendent's report ... 1908.
  - V.16-35 Stepney Employment Exchange, 34 (Reel 11)
    Stepney Employment Exchange. [Letter to Central Employed Body for London re riverside work].
  - V.16-36 unemployed men to Railway Companies, 35 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. [Letter concerning regulations for supplying lists of unemployed men to Railway Companies].
  - V.16-37 Employment Exchanges Committee, 1907; 36 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Agenda, reports, etc., for meetings ... 25th November 1907.
  - V.16-38 Employment Exchanges Committee, 1908; 37 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Agenda, reports, etc., for meetings ... 27th January 1908.
  - V.16-39 Employment Exchanges Committee, 1908; 38 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Agenda, reports, etc., for meetings ...13th April 1908.
  - V.16-40 Employment Exchanges Committee, 1908; 39 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Agenda, reports, etc., for meetings ... 4th May 1908.
  - V.16-41 Report and recommendations of Local Advisory Committees, 1908; 40 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Report and recommendations of Local Advisory Committees. 1908.
  - V.16-42 Report by Organising Superintendents on various matters, 1908; 41 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Report by Organising Superintendents on various matters, 4th May 1908.
  - V.16-43 Report by Organising Superintendents on various matters, 1908; 42 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Report by Organising Superintendents on various matters, 13th April 1908.
  - V.16-44 Report by the Superintendent, 1907; 43 (Reel 11)
    City of London Exchange. Report by the Superintendent ... upon the work carried out ... since ... December 1907.
  - V.16-45 Proposed scheme of co-operation, 44 (Reel 11)
    Proposed scheme of co-operation between the Committees of the Apprenticeship and Skilled Employment Association and the Employment Exchanges.
  - V.16-46 Instructions to Superintendents, 45 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Instructions to Superintendents.
  - V.16-47 Scheme for the constitution of Local Advisory Committees, 46 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Metropolitan Employment Exchanges. Scheme for the constitution of Local Advisory Committees.
  - V.16-48 Summary statement of objects, 47 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Metropolitan Employment Exchanges. Summary statement of objects.
  - V.16-49 Points to be emphasised in preliminary statement at the first meetings of the Local Advisory Committees, 48 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Points to be emphasised in preliminary statement at the first meetings of the Local Advisory Committees.
  - V.16-50 Letter concerning Local Advisory Committee, 1907; 49 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. (Letter concerning Local Advisory Committee). 1907.
  - V.16-51 Particulars of attendances of members of Local Advisory Committees, 1908; 50 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Particulars of attendances of members of Local Advisory Committees yet to be reconstituted. 1908.
  - V.16-52 Report of the Organising Superintendent, 1907; 51 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committees. Report of the Organising Superintendent on proceedings and recommendations of Committees. 1907.
  - V.16-53 Report of the Organising Superintendent, 1907; 52 (Reel 11)
  - V.16-54 Report of the Organising Superintendent, 1907; 53 (Reel 11)
  - V.16-55 Report of proceedings and recommendations of Local Advisory Committees, 1907; 54 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Report of proceedings and recommendations of Local Advisory Committees, with notes thereon by Organising Superintendent. November 1907.
  - V.16-56 Report of proceedings and recommendations of Local Advisory Committees, 1908; 55 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Report of proceedings and recommendations of Local Advisory Committees, with notes thereon by Organising Superintendent. January 1908.
  - V.16-57 Summary of proceedings of Local Advisory Committees, 1907; 56 (Reel 11)
    Summary of proceedings of Local Advisory Committees, 25th June 1907.
  - V.16-58 Report and recommendations of Local Advisory Committees, 1908; 57 (Reel 11)
  - V.16-59 Lewisham Advisory Committee, 58 (Reel 11)
    Lewisham Advisory Committee. [Two letters concerning Labour Exchanges].
  - V.16-60 Report of Organising Superintendent on recommendations, 59 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Employment Exchanges Committee. Local Advisory Committees. Report of Organising Superintendent on recommendations made to date.
  - V.16-61 Agenda of meeting of Local Advisory Committee, 1907; 60 (Reel 11)
    Lewisham Employment Exchange. Agenda of meeting of Local Advisory Committee ... held ... 8th November 1907.
  - V.16-62 Conference between the Advisory Committee of the Lewisham Employment Exchange and representatives of Local Trade Union Branches, 61 (Reel 11)
    Lewisham Employment Exchange. Conference between the Advisory Committee of the Lewisham Employment Exchange and representatives of Local Trade Union Branches ... 1907. Agenda.
  - V.16-63 Poplar Employment Exchange, 1907; 62 (Reel 11)
    Poplar Employment Exchange. [Letter of invitation to a meeting of Employers and Employees' representatives ... 1907].
  - V.17 Analysis of the rules of Trade Unions, 1908; 63 (Reel 11)
    Analysis of the rules of Trade Unions relating to unemployed, sick and accident benefits, and expenditure on such benefits by each Union in 1908.
  - V.18 Third ( -Eighth) report, 1907-1914; 64 (Reel 11)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Third ( -Eighth) report ... from 1 July 1907 to June 1914.
- London, Central (Unemployed) Body for London, Minutes, 1908-1910 (V.19.). Central (Unemployed) Body for London, Proceedings, 1914-1915.. (V.20. ) (Reel 12)
  - V.19-1 Minutes of proceedings, 1908; 1 (Reel 12)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. [Minutes of proceedings on] 6 (and 20) November 1908. Vol IV, nos 1 and 2.
  - V.19-2 Minutes of proceedings, 1908; 2 (Reel 12)
  - V.19-3 Agenda for meeting, 1908; 3 (Reel 12)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. [Agenda for] meeting on 4 December 1908.
  - V.19-4 Minutes of proceedings, 1909; 4 (Reel 12)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. [Minutes for proceedings on] 17 February 1909. Vol IV, no. 7.
  - V.19-5 Agenda for meeting, 1909; 5 (Reel 12)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. [Agenda for] meeting ... on ... 5 March 1909.
  - V.19-6 Minutes of proceedings, 1908-1909; 6 (Reel 12)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Index to Vol IV. Minutes of proceedings, from 6 November 1908 - 16 July 1909.
  - V.19-7 Minutes of proceedings, 1910; 7 (Reel 12)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. [Minutes of proceedings on] 21 January (and 4 and 18 February) 1910. Vol V, nos 7-9.
  - V.19-8 Minutes of proceedings, 1910; 8 (Reel 12)
  - V.19-9 Minutes of proceedings, 1910; 9 (Reel 12)
  - V.19-10 Agenda for meeting, 10 (Reel 12)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. [Agenda for] meeting ... on ... 18 February 1910.
  - V.20 Minutes of proceedings, 1914-1915; 11 (Reel 12)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Minutes of proceedings, 2 October 1914 to 23 July 1915. Vol X and index.